(Leonard:)All right, here's the deal.
(Leonard:)Sheldon is gone, so the tree
decorating rules are out the window.
(Penny:)Yeah, which means
we don't have to use
(Penny:)his ridiculous
ornament-spacing template.
(Leonard:)And I'm happy to report
its Kickstarter campaign
(Leonard:)is holding strong at zero dollars.
(Raj:)Wait, so Star Wars
and Star Trek characters
(Raj:)can go on the same branch?
(Leonard:)I know, it's crazy.
Welcome to the Thunderdome, people!
Woo!
(Howard:)I've never done this before.
It's kind of fun.
(Raj:)Yeah, if your mom could see
her little Bar Mitzvah boy right now,
(Raj:)she'd have a heart attack.
(Bernadette:)Good idea, I'll take a picture.
(Penny:)Honey, I'm a little strapped
for cash this year,
(Penny:)so for Christmas I was
thinking of giving you...
(Penny:)...this.
(Leonard:)I love it.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)But it is what you got me last year.
(Penny:)-Yeah.
-And last night.
(Stuart:)Hello.